A Guide to the Island Resources Foundation records FA1200
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1962, 1964, 1967-2016; 4; 13.67 Cubic Feet 36 letter document boxes
  - Adams, John, 1976-1977, 1979-1980, 1985, 1994, 1996-1997 (Box 152, Folder 1760)
  - Albuquerque, Klaus de, 1977-1981, 1983-1987, 1990, 1995-1999 (Box 152, Folder 1761)
  - American Airlines, 1971, 1973-1979, 1991, 1995 (Box 152, Folder 1762)
  - American Airlines, Fund Raising, 1974-2001 (Box 152, Folder 1763)
  - American Airlines, Paul Gibson, Jr., 1971-1974, 1976-1979, 1981, 1985, 1987, 2001 (Box 152, Folder 1764)
  - American Committee for International Conservation, Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, Announcements, etc, 1975-1977, 1979, 1982-1987 (Box 153, Folder 1765)
  - American Conservation Association, 1970-1977, 1980, 1984-1986, 1989 (Box 153, Folder 1766)
  - American Samoa, 1973-1974, 1977, 1984-1985, 1991-1992 (Box 153, Folder 1768)
  - Anguilla, 1982-1983, 1986, 1997, 1999-2000 (Box 153, Folder 1769)
  - Anguilla, Anguilla National Trust and Anguilla Archaeological and Historical Society, 1982, 1985-1986, 1991, 1997, 2009 (Box 153, Folder 1770)
  - Anguilla, Correspondence with Government, 1975-1986, 1991-1992, 1995-1996 (Box 153, Folder 1771)
  - Antigua, 1975, 1977-1978, 1980-1982, 1986, 1989-1990, 2008 (Box 153, Folder 1772)
  - Antigua, Correspondence with Desmond Nelson, Archaeological and Historical Society, 1977-1978, 1980-1981, 1984, 1986-1988, 1992, 2006, 2009 (Box 153, Folder 1773)
  - Antigua, Correspondence with Government, 1977-1978, 1984-1986, 1990-1992, 1995-1996, 1998-2000 (Box 153, Folder 1774)
  - Antigua, Correspondence with Ted Stevens, 1977-1980, 1983-1985 (Box 153, Folder 1775)
  - Antigua, Historic Site Commission, 1976-1978 (Box 153, Folder 1776)
  - Antigua, LISA (Leeward Islands Science Association), 1984-1986 (Box 153, Folder 1777)
  - Antigua, Nelson's Dockyard, Friends of the English Harbour, 1975, 1977-1978, 1983-1986, 1999 (Box 153, Folder 1778)
  - Archbold, John D., 1970, 1973-1989, 1993-1994 (Box 153, Folder 1779)
  - Archbold Tropical Research Center, 1991-1996, 2000 (Box 154, Folder 1780)
  - Associations of Caribbean Universities, Philip Sherlock, 1972-1976, 1978, 1983, 1986, 1994 (Box 154, Folder 1781)
  - Association of Island Marine Laboratories of the Caribbean, 1973, 1976, 1981, 1983-1985, 1989, 1996 (Box 154, Folder 1782)
  - Atlantic Center for the Environment, 1984-1988, 1991, 1994-1996, 1998-2000, 2004, 2006, 2008, 2010, 2015 (Box 154, Folder 1783)
  - Auble, Helen, 1964, 1970, 1979-1980, 1983, 1986-1987, 1989-1992, 1996 (Box 154, Folder 1784)
  - Auble, Helen, Bequest, 1988, 1998 (Box 154, Folder 1785)
  - "B" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1994-1999, 2001-2002 (Box 154, Folder 1786)
  - Bahamas, 1972-1973, 19765-1977, 1980, 1991, 1993, 1999 (Box 154, Folder 1787)
  - Barbados, 1975, 1977-1978, 1982, 1988, 1991-1992, 1996-1998 (Box 154, Folder 1788)
  - Barbados, Barbados Museum and Historical Society, 1978-1979, 1983-1986, 1988-1991, 1997 (Box 154, Folder 1789)
  - Barbados, Correspondence with Government of Barbados, 1972-1975, 1978, 1980, 1985-1988, 1990, 1995-1996, 1998 (Box 154, Folder 1790)
  - Barbados, Ministry of External Affairs, Algernon Symmonds, 1976, 1978 (Box 154, Folder 1791)
  - Bellairs Research Institute of McGill University, 1969-1972, 1975, 1977, 1979, 1981-1982, 1985-1987, 1989, 1996 (Box 155, Folder 1793)
  - Beller, William S., 1972, 1974-1975, 1977-1988, 1990, 1996 (Box 155, Folder 1794)
  - Bermuda, 1999, 2001 (Box 155, Folder 1795)
  - Bermuda, Bermuda Aquarium, Museum and Zoo, 1995-1997 (Box 155, Folder 1796)
  - Bermuda, Bermuda National Trust, 1972, 1998 (Box 155, Folder 1797)
  - Bermuda, Biological Station for Research, 1971-1974, 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 155, Folder 1798)
  - Bermuda, Commission of Inquiry, 1971, 1990-1991 (Box 155, Folder 1799)
  - Bermuda, Government of Bermuda, 1973, 1980-1982, 1990-1996, 2000 (Box 155, Folder 1800)
  - Bermuda, David B. Wingate, 1972-1973, 1976-1977 (Box 155, Folder 1801)
  - Bernhard, Robert A., 1971-1981, 1983, 1985 (Box 155, Folder 1802)
  - Biays, W. Tuckerman and Alice, 1982, 1984-1986, 1994 (Box 155, Folder 1803)
  - Bird Life International (Formerly International Council for Bird Preservation), 1987, 1990-1993, 1996-1998 (Box 155, Folder 1804)
  - Blake, Barry F., 1995-2000 (Box 155, Folder 1805)
  - Blum, Jonathan P., 1974-1983, 1988, 2011 (Box 155, Folder 1806)
  - British Development Division, Department for International Development (DFID), United Kingdom Foreign and Commonwealth Office (FCO), 1971-1974, 1987, 1988, 2000-2002, 2005, 2010 (Box 155, Folder 1807)
  - British Virgin Islands, Island Resources Foundation Registration, 1999-2016 (Box 156, Folder 1808)
  - British Virgin Islands, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1974, 1995-1996, 1998, 2000, 2002, 2004, 2014 (Box 156, Folder 1809)
  - British Virgin Islands, Onions Bouchard and McCulloch Ltd., 1996-1997, 2000 (Box 156, Folder 1810)
  - British Virgin Islands, Registration for Non-Profit Organisations (NPO) Act of 2012, 2013-2016 (Box 156, Folder 1811)
  - British Virgin Islands Government, 1974-1976, 1978, 1982-1983, 1999-2007, 2009, 2011 (Box 156, Frame 1812)
  - British Virgin Islands Government, Chief Minister's Office, 1972-1978, 1982-1985, 1998-2003, 2007, 2009 (Box 156, Folder 1813)
  - British Virgin Islands Government, Governor's Office, 1972, 1974-1976, 1982, 1991 (Box 156, Folder 1814)
  - British Virgin Islands Government, Ministry of Natural Resources, 1974-1981, 1984, 1986-1987, 1990-1992, 1999-2000, 2002-2003, 2009-2010 (Box 156, Folder 1815)
  - British Virgin Islands Government, Town and Country Planning, 1977-1978, 1994, 1996-2000, 2002, 2004, 2006, 2008-2009 (Box 156, Folder 1816)
  - British Virgin Islands, H. Lavity Stoutt Community College, General Correspondence, 1996-2013 (Box 156, Folder 1817)
  - British Virgin Islands, H. Lavity Stoutt Community College, Board of Governors, 2003-2006, 2010 (Box 156, Folder 1818)
  - British Virgin Islands, H. Lavity Stoutt Community College, Centre for Applied Marine Studies, 2000-2008 (Box 156, Folder 1819)
  - British Virgin Islands, H. Lavity Stoutt Community College, Miscellaneous Information, 1996, 1999-2001, 2003-2011 (Box 157, Folder 1820)
  - British Virgin Islands, H. Lavity Stoutt Community College, Memoranda of Agreement and Library Donation, 1996-2002, 2006-2011 (Box 157, Folder 1821-1822)
  - British Virgin Islands, Marine Archaeology Resource, Development Conservation and Management, 1987-1988 (Box 157, Folder 1823)
  - British Virgin Islands, Smiths Gore, 1996, 2000-2001, 2008 (Box 157, Folder 1824)
  - "C" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986-1999, 2001, 2004 (Box 157, Folder 1825)
  - Cambers, Gillian, 1986, 1989, 1996-2002, 2006, 2009 (Box 157, Folder 1826)
  - Caribbean Action for Sustainable Tourism (CAST), 1998-2000 (Box 157, Folder 1827)
  - Caribbean Agricultural Research and Development Institute (CARDI), 1982, 1984, 1986, 1988-1989, 1995 (Box 157, Folder 1828)
  - Caribbean and Western Atlantic Marine Educators Association, 1999, 2001 (Box 157, Folder 1829)
  - Caribbean Association of Environmental Health Officers (CAEHO), 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 157, Folder 1830)
  - Caribbean Challenge Initiative, 2011, 2013-2015 (Box 157, Folder 1831)
  - Caribbean Community (CARICOM), 1978, 1980, 1982, 1986-1989, 1991, 1993, 1995-1998, 2006 (Box 158, Folder 1832)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association (CCA), General Correspondence, 1986-2011, 2013 (Box 158, Folder 1833-1834)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association (CCA), Annual Meeting, Martinique, 1988 (Box 158, Folder 1835)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association (CCA), Annual Meeting, St. Croix, 1991 (Box 158, Folder 1836)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association (CCA), Annual Meeting, Trinidad and Tobago, 1992 (Box 158, Folder 1837)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association (CCA), CCA Secretary Correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 158, Folder 1838)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association (CCA), Correspondence with Jill Sheppard/Secretariat, 1976-1984, 1986 (Box 158, Folder 1839)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association (CCA), Correspondence with President and Board, 1977-1980, 1983, 1985-1990, 1998-2001, 2007, 2009, 2013 (Box 159, Folder 1840)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association (CCA), Executive Director Correspondence, 1979, 1986-2007, 2010-2011 (Box 159, Folder 1841-1842)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association (CCA), General Information, 1978, 1982, 1985-1987, 1990, 2007-2010 (Box 159, Folder 1843)
  - Caribbean Conservation Association (CCA), Technical Advisory Group, 1989-1991 (Box 159, Folder 1844)
  - Caribbean Conservation Corporation, Colin Phipps, 1980, 1983, 1985, 1987, 1994, 2010 (Box 159, Folder 1845)
  - Caribbean Council for Science and Technology (CCST), 1993, 1996-1997 (Box 159, Folder 1849)
  - Caribbean Development Bank, 1973-1974, 1976, 1978-1982, 1989, 1991, 1997-2000, 2002, 2005 (Box 159, Folder 1847)
  - Caribbean Development Bank, Information, 1993-1994, 1997-2000, 2002-2004, 2006, 2008 (Box 159, Folder 1848)
  - Caribbean Disaster Emergency Response Agency (CDERA), 1990, 1994-1996, 1999, 2005, 2009 (Box 160, Folder 1849)
  - Caribbean Environment and Development Institute (CEDI), 1992-2000 (Box 160, Folder 1850)
  - Caribbean Environmental Health Institute (CEHI), 1990, 1992, 1995, 2000, 2002-2003, 2006-2007 (Box 160, Folder 1851)
  - Caribbean Fisheries Management Council, 1996-1997 (Box 160, Folder 1852)
  - Caribbean Hotel Association, 1986, 1991-1992, 1996-1999 (Box 160, Folder 1853)
  - Caribbean Large Marine Ecosystem Programme (CLME), 2009-2011 (Box 160, Folder 1854)
  - Caribbean Latin American Action, Formerly Caribbean Central American Action, 1980-1982, 1986-1987, 1992-1993 (Box 160, Folder 1855)
  - Caribbean Marine Biological Institute, 1970-1978 (Box 160, Folder 1856)
  - Caribbean Marine Protected Area Management (CaMPAM), 2001-2003, 2014 (Box 160, Folder 1857)
  - Caribbean Natural Resources Institute (CANARI), 1992-1995, 1998, 2000-2002, 2005, 2009, 2011-2012 (Box 160, Folder 1858)
  - Caribbean Natural Resources Institute (CANARI), Information, 1987-1989, 1992-1998, 2001-2002, 2005-2006, 2009, 2012-2013 (Box 160, Folder 1859)
  - Caribbean Network for Integrated Rural Development (CNIRD), 1988, 1990, 1998 (Box 160, Folder 1860)
  - Caribbean Planning for Adaptation to Climate Change (CPACC), 1999-2002, 2004 (Box 161, Folder 1861)
  - Caribbean Policy Development Centre, 1994-1995, 2003-2004 (Box 161, Folder 1862)
  - Caribbean Regional Environmental Programme (CREP), 2001-2004 (Box 161, Folder 1863)
  - Caribbean Studies Association, 1977-1979, 1984, 1992, 1997 (Box 161, Folder 1864)
  - Caribbean Tourism Organization, 1973-1977, 1979, 1986, 1988-1990, 1994 (Box 161, Folder 1865)
  - Caribbean Volunteer Expeditions (CVE), 1994-1996, 1999-2004, 2006-2007, 2009-2010 (Box 161, Folder 1866)
  - Caribbean Waste and Watershed Association (CWWA), 1991 (Box 161, Folder 1867)
  - CIDA (Canadian International Development Agency)/Canadian High Commission, 1974-1975, 1987-1989 (Box 161, Folder 1868)
  - Cayman Islands, General Correspondence, 1974-1976, 1985, 1987-1988, 1991, 1995-1996, 1999 (Box 161, Folder 1869)
  - Cayman Islands, Correspondence with Government, 1973-1975, 1985-1987, 1991, 1997 (Box 161, Folder 1870)
  - CH2M Hill, 1999 (Box 161, Folder 1871)
  - Cintron, Gilberto, 1970, 1975, 1977-1982, 1985 (Box 161, Folder 1872)
  - Commission for Environmental Cooperation (CEC), 1998-1999 (Box 161, Folder 1873)
  - Commonwealth Science Council, 1985-1989 (Box 161, Folder 1874)
  - Conservation International, 1987-1988, 2001-2002, 2005 (Box 161, Folder 1875)
  - Consortium of Caribbean Universities for Natural Resource Management (CCUNRM), 1991, 1993 (Box 161, Folder 1876)
  - Coolidge, Harold J., 1979-1980, 1982-1986, 1989, 1991, 1994-1995, 1998-1999 (Box 162, Folder 1877)
  - Coral Reef Initiative, Coral Reef Alliance, 1994-1995, 1999, 2001-2002, 2005 (Box 162, Folder 1878)
  - Coral World, 1997-2003, 2006 (Box 162, Folder 1879)
  - CORALINA, 1997-2009, 2011-2012 (Box 162, Folder 1880-1881)
  - CORALINA, CORALINA and Center for Marine Conservation, 1999-2000 (Box 162, Folder 1882)
  - CORALINA, GEF Proposal to World Bank, 1998-2003, 2010 (Box 163, Folder 1883)
  - Cordell, John, 1984-1986 (Box 163, Folder 1884)
  - Costa Rica, 1972-1973, 1975-1976, 1982 (Box 163, Folder 1885)
  - Cotter, James, 1982, 1997, 1999 (Box 163, Folder 1886)
  - Critical Ecosystem Partnership Fund (CEPF), 2011-2013 (Box 163, Folder 1887)
  - Critical Ecosystem Partnership Fund (CEPF), Information, 2009, 2012-2014 (Box 163, Folder 1888)
  - Cropper Foundation, 2002-2003, 2008 (Box 163, Folder 1889)
  - "D" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986-1992, 1994-2000 (Box 163, Folder 1890)
  - da Costa, Henrique Pinto, 1993, 1995-2004, 2011-2012 (Box 163, Folder 1891)
  - da Costa, Henrique Pinto, Promoting Forest Conservation in Principe, 2007 (Box 163, Folder 1892)
  - da Costa, Henrique Pinto, Resume, Articles, Information, 1993, 2002 (Box 163, Folder 1894)
  - da Costa, Henrique Pinto, Soa Tome Environmental Profile, Proposal, 1995 (Box 163, Folder 1894)
  - da Costa, Henrique Pinto, Sao Tome Biodiversity Conservation, 2005-2007 (Box 164, Folder 1895)
  - Dalhousie University, 1984-1985, 1987-1992, 1994-1995, 1997-1999 (Box 164, Folder 1896)
  - Dewey, Richard, 1974, 1976, 1978-1979, 1981-1982, 1984-1985, 1987-1989 (Box 164, Folder 1897)
  - Dickinson, Joshua C., III, Tropical Research and Development, Inc., 1983, 1986-1989, 1991-1993 (Box 164, Folder 1898)
  - Dominica, 1981-1983, 1986, 1998, 2000-2001 (Box 164, Folder 1899)
  - Dominica, Correspondence with Ministry of Agriculture/Forest and Parks Department, 1973, 1975-1982, 19884-1987, 1993, 1997, 2000, 2009 (Box 164, Folder 1900)
  - Dominica, Government Correspondence Except Ministry of Agriculture/Parks Department, 1973-1975, 1980, 1982, 1993-1994, 1997-1999 (Box 164, Folder 1901)
  - Dominica, Caribbean Southern Corporation, 1979 (Box 164, Folder 1902)
  - Dominica Forestry Development, 1980-1983 (Box 164, Folder 1903)
  - Dominican Republic, 1974-1981, 1984, 1987, 1993, 1997-2000 (Box 164, Folder 1904)
  - Downs, Michael, 1997-2003, 2005 (Box 164, Folder 1905)
  - Dubois, Random, 1979-1980, 1982, 1984, 1986-1988, 1991, 1996-1999, 2002, 2004 (Box 164, Folder 1906)
  - "E" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986-1988, 1991-1998, 2002-2003 (Box 165, Folder 1907)
  - East-West Center, 1981-1985, 1988-1989, 1993 (Box 165, Folder 1908)
  - Eastern Caribbean Center, University of the Virgin Islands, 1991, 1994-1996, 1998 (Box 165, Folder 1909)
  - Eastern Caribbean Institute of Agriculture and Forestry, 1994 (Box 165, Folder 1910)
  - Eastern Caribbean Organisation of Development Foundations, 1987, 1990, 1992-1993, 1995 (Box 165, Folder 1911)
  - Eckstein, Mark, 1991-1992, 1998-1999 (Box 165, Folder 1912)
  - Environmental Protection in the Caribbean, 2003-2005, 2007, 2010-2011 (Box 165, Folder 1913)
  - "F" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986-1992, 1995, 1997, 2000-2001 (Box 165, Folder 1914)
  - Fairbairn, Patrick, 1980-1984 (Box 165, Folder 1915)
  - Fauna and Flora International, 1999-2002, 2005, 2009 (Box 165, Folder 1916)
  - Fire Island, 1970-1972, 1976-1978, 1982-1983, 1997-1999, 2001-2002 (Box 165, Folder 1917-1918)
  - Florida Association of Voluntary Agencies for Caribbean Action (FAVA/CA), 1987-1988, 1990, 1992-2003, 2007 (Box 165, Folder 1919)
  - Florida International University, 1972-1974, 1978, 1986, 1996, 1998 (Box 165, Folder 1920)
  - Ford Foundation, 1980-1982 (Box 166, Folder 1921)
  - Fortwangler, Crystal, 1997-1999, 2001-2003, 2005, 2009 (Box 166, Folder 1922)
  - Foster, Franklin (Wink), 1967-1970, 1972-1974, 1978. 1980-1984 (Box 166, Folder 1923)
  - Freeman, Peter, 1974-1975, 1977, 1979-1984, 1991, 2004-2005 (Box 166, Folder 1924)
  - "G" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986-2002 (Box 166, Folder 1925)
  - Ganman, John K., 1988-1989, 1991, 2001 (Box 166, Folder 1926)
  - Gardner, Lloyd, 1994, 1996-2006, 2010-2014 (Box 166, Folder 1927-1928)
  - Global Environment Facility (GEF), 1994-1998, 2014 (Box 166, Folder 1929)
  - Global International Waters Assessment (GIWA), 2001 (Box 166, Folder 1930)
  - Global Island Partnership (GLISPA), 2007-2014 (Box 166, Folder 1931)
  - Global Islands Network, Island Web Consortium, 1996-1999, 2001-2003, 2007, 2014 (Box 167, Folder 1932-1933)
  - Goldman Environmental Foundation, 1996-2000, 2002-2003 (Box 167, Folder 1934)
  - Goodwin, Melvin H., Environmental Research Projects, 1978-1989, 1992, 1997, 2001 (Box 167, Folder 1935)
  - Goodwin, Melvin H., Information on Environmental Research Projects, 1977, 1984 (Box 167, Folder 1936)
  - Grenada, 1979-1988, 1990-1993, 1995-1996, 1998 (Box 167, Folder 1937)
  - "H" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986-1993, 1995-2000, 2002-2004 (Box 167, Folder 1938)
  - Hamilton, Larry, 1993-1994 (Box 167, Folder 1939)
  - Hanif, Mahamad, 1971, 1973-1976, 1978-1980, 1984-1987, 1993 (Box 167, Folder 1940)
  - Harvard University, 1985, 1987-1989, 1991, 1993, 1994 (Box 167, Folder 1941)
  - Hawaii, Correspondence with Government, 1971-1972, 1975-1977, 1979 (Box 167, Folder 1942)
  - Hawaii, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1973-1977, 1981-1982, 1985-1987 (Box 167, Folder 1943)
  - Hodge, Walter, 1994, 2000-2001, 2004, 2013-2014 (Box 168, Folder 1944)
  - Hokin, Myron, 1972-1979, 1981-1984, 1986, 1993-1994, 2004-2005 (Box 168, Folder 1945)
  - Homeland Foundation, 1988-1993 (Box 168, Folder 1946)
  - Howell, Christopher, 1973, 1987, 1996-2001, 2003-2004 (Box 168, Folder 1947)
  - Hughes, Alister, 1975-1984, 1986, 1988, 1991-2005, 2008-2011, 2013 (Box 168, Folder 1948-1949)
  - "I" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1985-1987, 1989-1992, 1994-1995, 2000 (Box 168, Folder 1950)
  - IDEAS (Institutional Development and Economic Affairs Service, Inc.), Administrative Correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box 168, Folder 1951)
  - Institute of Marine Affairs (IMA), 1979, 1981-1985, 1987, 1989, 1994, 1999 (Box 168, Folder 1952)
  - Institute of Tropical Forestry, US Department of Agriculture, 1986, 1990-1992, 1995, 2001, 2003-2004, 2008, 2014 (Box 168, Folder 1953)
  - INSULA, 1994-1997 (Box 168, Folder 1954)
  - Inter-American Biodiversity Information Network (IABIN), 1998, 2002, 2004 (Box 169, Folder 1955)
  - Inter-American Development Bank, 1977-1979, 1991, 1993-1995, 1998-1999, 2001 (Box 169, Folder 1956)
  - Inter-American Development Bank, Registration, 1995 (Box 169, Folder 1957)
  - Inter-American Foundation, 1983, 1987, 1992, 1994 (Box 169, Folder 1958)
  - Inter-American Institute for Cooperation on Agriculture (IICA), 1988, 1991-1992, 1994 (Box 169, Folder 1959)
  - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), Caribbean Program Office, 1975-1976, 2001-2003 (Box 169, Folder 1960)
  - International Small Islands Studies Association, 1992, 1998, 2000-2002, 2009, 2012, 2014 (Box 169, Folder 1961)
  - The International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources (IUCN)-The World Conservation Union, 1972-1980, 1982, 1984-1988, 1990-1998, 2009-2010 (Box 169, Folder 1962)
  - The International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources (IUCN)-The World Conservation Union, Correspondence with Commission of National Parks and Protected Areas, 1983-1989, 1992, 1997, 2004-2005 (Box 169, Folder 1963)
  - The International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources (IUCN)-The World Conservation Union, Correspondence with Director General, 1979-1980, 1982, 1984-1989 (Box 169, Folder 1964)
  - The International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources (IUCN)-The World Conservation Union, Commission on Environmental strategy and Planning, 1979, 1981-1983, 1985, 1988-1989, 1991-1998, 2000, 2012 (Box 169, Folder 1965)
  - The International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources (IUCN)-The World Conservation Union, General information, 1989, 1993-1994, 1996, 2005 (Box 169, Folder 1966)
  - The International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources (IUCN)-The World Conservation Union, "Islands" Initiative, Frederic Briand Correspondence, 1972, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 170, Folder 1967)
  - The International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources (IUCN)-The World Conservation Union, Washington Office, Meeting, 1993-1995, 1998-1999, 2005, 2008-2009 (Box 170, Folder 1968)
  - IO CARIBE, 1976-1977, 1982 (Box 170, Folder 1969)
  - IO CARIBE, Background, 1972-1973, 1975-1976 (Box 170, Folder 1970)
  - ISISA, Islands of the World Conference, XII, 2009-2012 (Box 170, Folder 1971)
  - Islands Magazine, 1992-1993, 1996-2001 (Box 170, Folder 1972)
  - Islands Research Foundation, 1975 (Box 170, Folder 1973)
  - Islands Research Foundation, Raine Edward Bennett Correspondence, 1962, 1971-1978 (Box 170, Folder 1974)
  - Ivie, Michael, 1995, 1997-2002, 2005, 2009 (Box 170, Folder 1975)
  - "J" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1985-1989, 1991-1993, 1995-1996, 1988-1999, 2001-2002 (Box 170, Folder 1976)
  - Jackson, Iver, 1982-1983, 1985-1986, 1990, 1998-1999 (Box 170, Folder 1977)
  - Jamaica, 1983-1985, 1988, 1990, 1992-1994, 1999 (Box 170, Folder 1978)
  - Jamaica, Correspondence with Government Agencies, 1973-1975, 1978, 1982-1983, 1985, 1991, 1993, 1997-1999 (Box 170, Folder 1979)
  - Institute of Jamaica, 1975-1976 (Box 171, Folder 1981)
  - Jarecki, Henry, 1980-1989, 1991-1992, 1994, 1996-1997, 1999-2003, 2005-2012, 2015 (Box 171, Folder 1981)
  - Jarecki, Henry, Donation of Peebles Hospital Equipment, 1981-1982 (Box 171, Folder 1982)
  - Jarecki, Lianna, 1995-1999, 2003-2005 (Box 171, Folder 1984)
  - Joseph, Daven, 1986-1988 (Box 171, Folder 1985)
  - "K" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986-1987, 1990-1992, 1997-1998, 2002 (Box 171, Folder 1986)
  - Karlsson, Gail, 1993, 1996, 1999, 2001-2005 (Box 171, Folder 1987)
  - Katalysis Foundation, 1989-1990, 1992-1994 (Box 171, Folder 1988)
  - Kaufmann, Milton, 1988, 2001-2006, 2008, 2015 (Box 171, Folder 1989)
  - Kew Gardens, 1985, 1988, 1997, 2001 (Box 171, Folder 1990)
  - "L" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986-1997, 1999, 2001 (Box 171, Folder 1991)
  - LaBastille, Anne, 1972-1986, 1988, 1997-2000, 2004, 2006, 2011 (Box 171, Folder 1992)
  - Lausche, Barbara, 1997-2006, 2008, 2010 (Box 171, Folder 1993)
  - Lewis, Lawrence W., 1981-1982, 1984-1986, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 172, Folder 1995)
  - Loukissas, Philippos, 1983-1987 (Box 172, Folder 1995)
  - "M" Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1985-2002, 2004, 2008 (Box 172, Folder 1996)
  - The John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, 1991, 1993-2002, 2007 (Box 172, Folder 1997)
  - McEachern, John, 1976-1981, 1985-1987, 1991, 1995-2001 (Box 172, Folder 1998)
  - McElroy, Jerome, 1973, 1979-1980, 1983-1994, 1997-1999, 2003, 2010-2011, 2014 (Box 172, Folder 1999)
  - MacFarlane, Euan, 1977-1979, 1982-1983, 1987-1989, 1996, 2005 (Box 172, Folder 2000)
  - Man and the Biosphere, US (MAB), Correspondence with Office of the Executive Director, 1977, 1979-1981, 1983-1989, 1993-1994, 2000-2001 (Box 172, Folder 2001)
  - Marine Resource and Environmental Management Program (MAREMP), 1994, 1997 (Box 172, Folder 2002)
  - Matheson, Lloyd, 1971, 1974-1975, 1977-1990, 1992, 1999-2000 (Box 173, Folder 2003)
  - May, Peter and Richard, 1978, 1980-1985, 1987, 1990-1991, 1994, 1997-2001 (Box 173, Folder 2004)
  - The Micronesia Institute, 1984, 1988-1989, 1991, 1999-2000 (Box 173, Folder 2005)
  - Miller, Norman, 1985-1986, 1988-1989, 2000-2001 (Box 173, Folder 2006)
  - Monitor International, 1999-2001 (Box 173, Folder 2007)
  - Monterey Institute of International Studies, 2002 (Box 173, Folder 2008)
  - Montserrat, Correspondence with Government Agencies, 1975, 1979-1980, 1985, 1987, 1994, 1997, 2008-2009 (Box 173, Folder 2009)
  - Montserrat, National Trust, 1974-1975, 1977-1978, 1980, 1982-1984, 1986-1987, 1991 (Box 173, Folder 2010)